

Josh Le Gresley

40 Sunset Ridge Drive, Bellingen, 2454 0413 088 280 | joshlegresley@hotmail.com

Summary.

Highly experienced farm hand with more than eleven years experience in livestock and arable farming. Proficient in the use of farming equipment and supplies. Effectively performing and assortment of duties, including milk harvesting, calf rearing, artificial insemination, tractor driving, repairing and maintaining farm equipment, property management, training and supervision of staff. More recently I have taken the opportunity to explore new horizons. Whilst being a stay at home parent for my two children I have been studying for a Bachalor of Computer Science full time, with the aim to become a software developer.

Employment History _____

Bellingen River Organics

Bellingen, NSW

Apr 2019 - Dec 2019

FARM WORKER (PART TIME)

- · Assisted in the cultivation, planting and harvesting of organic produce
- Demonstrated the ability to apply former skills to a variety of working contexts
- Exhibited the ability to adhere to role expectations and take responsible initiative where necessary
- Effectively communicated and collaborated with colleagues and management to ensure continuity in following sustainably friendly practices, safe procedures and timely collection of produce

Raleigh Dairies Raleigh, NSW

Dairy Farm Hand Nov 2014 - Jan 2018

- · Worked competently and confidently both in an individual setting as well as collaboratively with colleagues
- · Developed specific goals and plans to prioritise, organise and accomplish daily work with little to no supervision
- · Operated and maintained various machinery such as relevant milking machinery and calf rearing equipment
- · Responsibly drove tractors, motorbikes/quadbikes and farm vehicle's to fulfil daily tasks such as herding, fence fixing and food distribution
- · Provided medical treatment, such as administering medications, vaccinations and assisting with birthing
- Directing, mentoring and monitoring the work of casual and seasonal workers

Harrimar P/L Mount Gambier, SA

Dairy Farm Hand

Jun 2014 - Nov 2014

- Maintained preventative maintenance and repairs on all farm machinery
- Showed diligence in promptness and reliability
- · Adhered to WHS health standards in sanitising and cleaning of general farming and milking equipment

Education_

University of New England

Armidale, NSW

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

Nov 2018 - Oct 2021 (Expected)

Camberwell College of Art and Design

London, UK

BACHELOR OF ARTS PHOTOGRAPHY

Sep 2006 - Jun 2009

References_

Company Director

Bellingen Valley Organics

CHRIS FLEMING

0497 175 170

hello@bellingerriverorganics.com.au

Farm Manager

Raleigh Dairies

BEN SCHATZMAN

0458 566 803